Finding Aid for the Cecil Sims
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous. Approximately 100 items, including flyers and blurbs, application forms, lists of names and addresses, and maps of France. Also included is a holographic paragraph signed by O.W. Holmes, dated March 8, 1931. (Box 25)
Campbell, Howell H., (1); Jan. 17, 1934; 6
Canddy, A., (1); Feb. 4, 1947; 6
Carmichael, O.C., (7); June 9, 1942, June 12, 1942, June 12, 1942, Aug. 17, 1942, Dec. 20, 1943, (to ~ordell Hull), Dec. 24, 1943, Jan. 25, 1963; 6
Carney, G.C., (1); Feb. 28, 1946; 6
Carney, H.K. Jr., (1); Hay 25, 1937; 6
Carothers, Howard, (1); Nov. 26, 1934; 6
Carpenter, Samuel L., Jr., (1); July 24, 1936; 6
Carr, Aubrey L., (1); Aug. 23, 1962; 6
Carr, Joe C., (1); Nov. 2, 1960; 6
Carr, W.M., (1); Aug. 29, 1933; 6
Castleman, Clydell, (2); Jan. 29, 1962, Nov. 15, 1962; 6
Castleman, Francis L., Jr., (1); Feb. 2, 1940 (to Fyke Farmer); 6
Catalano, Richard M., (1); Apr. 23, 1964; 6
Cate, John M., (1); Feb. 12, 1946; 6
Caudill, Noble C., (2); June 12,1959, Mar. 2, 1965; 6
Caudle, Theron Lemar, (1); Feb. 18, 1952; 6
Chaffin, Nora C., (1); July 30, 1962; 6
Chambers, Louis, (l); Nov. 8, 1938; 6
Chambers, M.M., (3); Aug. 23, 1960, Aug. 29, 1960, Sept. 9, 1960; 6
Chambliss, Jac, (1); Jan. 29, 1957; 6
Chandler, Edna White, (1); May 24, 1961 (to WilliamS. Vaughn); 6
Chandler, Walter, (13); Jan. 12, 1933, May 15, 1936, May 29, 1936, June 2, 1936, June 3, 1936, Mar. 29, 1937, Aug. 31, 1937, Sept. 21, 1937, Sept. 21, 1937 (to John J. Gore), Mar. 19, 1938, Mar. 29, 1938, Apr. 5, 1938, (n.d.). (to Charles Nelson); 6
Chapman, H.H., (1); Aug. 13, 1936; 6
Cheatham, Elliott E., (10); Dec. 2, 1961, Apr. 10, 1962, Aug. 12, 1962, Feb. 16, 1963, May 7, 1963, July 31, 1963, Apr. 25, 1964, Oct. 17, 1966, (n.d.), (n.d.); 6
Cheney, tlrainard, (1); Oct. 30, 1956; 6
Cheshire, J. Ross Jr., (1); June 30, 1964; 6
Chilton, W.M., (1); June 13, 1935; 6
Chitwood, Harry H., (2); Feb. 9, 1954, June 29, 1955; 6
Claitor, Otto, (1); Oct. 7, 1939; 6
Clark, Hale A., (1); Apr. 12, 1949 (to ’ferry Hart); 6
Clark, Iris Moore, (1); June 15, 1942; 6
Clark, Robert B. Jr., (2); June 7, 1947, July 15, 1948; 6
Clark, R. Hix, (1); Nov. 12, 1964; 6
Clark, Wallace, (1); Apr. 26, 1938; 6
Clarke, H.B., (1); Feb. 20, 1939; 6
Clawson, M. Don, (27); Dec. 4, 1947, Jan. 15, 1949, ~~r. 3, 1949, Dec. 20, 1949 (to Gordon ~rowning), Jan. 13, 1950, Feb. 16, 1950,
Clawson, M. Don, cont.; Feb. 18, 1950, Feb. 18, 1950, Feb. 18, 1950, Feb. 24, 1950, Feb. 24, 1950, Mar. 12, 1950, Apr. 1, 1950, Apr. 3, 1950, Apr. 3, 1950, Apr. 3, 1950, Apr. 4, 1950, Apr. 7, 1950, Apr. 10, 1950 (to Emory Morris), Apr. 13, J950 (to Hobert A. Lambert), Apr. 13, 1950, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.); 6
Clemenco, S.H., (1); May 17, 1961; 6
Clement, Anna Belle, (1); Apr. 12, 1965; 7
Ceement, Frank G., (4); Dec. 8, 1953, Jan. 27, 1955, Dec. 19, 1955, Sept. 28, 1957; 7
Claments, C.R., (1); Nov. 4, 1943; 6
Clements, Earle C., (1); July 23, 1948; 7
Clements, Hal H., (1); Apr. 4, 1933; 7
Cochran, S.D., (4); Sept. 9, 1941, Sept. 12, 1941, Apr. 30, (n.d.); 7
Coeen, J.W., (l); Feb. 26, 1962 (to Grace Sims Irvin); 7
Coffman, Dale, (1); July 2, 1946; 7
Cohn, Fletcher,G., (1); May 26, 1959; 7
Coile, W.W., (1); July 10, 1933; 7
Cole, Ashley, (1); Oct. 19, 1962; 7
Cole, G.H., (1); (n.d.); 7
Cole, Philip, (2); May 20, 1942, July 27, 1943; 7
Coleman, W.L., (1); Dec. 17, 1937; 7
Collins, Mary, (1); Sept. 23, 1949 (to Mary Woodall); 7
Colville, Mrs. John L., (1); July 30, 1956; 7
Comer, Donald, (1); Aug. 10, 1948; 7
Conley, E.T., (1); Sept. 22, 1936; 7
Cook, G.W. Jr., (1); Oct. 31, 1942; 7
Coolidge, Richard N., (1); Apr. 18, 1949; 7
Cooney, Hobert G., (1); Sept. 1, 1941; 7
Cooper, J.W., (1); Hay 5, 1938; 7
Cooper, Jere, (4); May 20, 1937, Apr. 4, 1938, July 281 1941, Aug. 8, 1944; 7
Cooper, Noah Webster, (1); (date illegible); 7
Cooper, Prentice, (2); Jan. 27, 1938, Mar. 30, 1939; 7
Cope, Quill E., (2); June 15, 1955 (to George F. McCanless), June 17, 1955;7
Coppedge, Calvin III, (1); (n.d.); 7
Cornelius, ~harles L. Jr., (1); Oct. 27, 1959; 7
Corson, H.H., (8); Feb. 8, 1933, Apr. 1933, Aug~ 17, 1933, Aug. 17, 1933, Oct. 14, 1933, Jan. 16, 1935, July 29, 1944, June 29, 1948; 7
Courtenay, Walter R., {1); Dec. 7, 1961; 7.
Courtney,, Wirt, (3); Mar. 27, 1933, Dec. 23, 1938, June 8, 1942; 7
Cousin, Sumter P., (4); Oct. 14, 1938, Oct. 14, 1938 (to Mack Fuqua), Nov. 9, 1938, Nov. 22, 1938 (to Marion G. Evans); 7
Covington, Fred, (1); May 6, 1963; 7
Cowan, Bonnie, (1); Jan. 24, 1963; 7
Cowell, Richard N., (1); Jan. 19, 1951; 7
Cox, Allen Jr., (1); June 21, 1962; 7
Cox, Jas. N., (2); Aug. 9, 1942, Aug. 13, 1942; 7
Cox, Thad. A., (10); May 9, 1934, May 9, 1934, May 9, 1934, May 16, 1934, Jan. 28, 1935, Mar. 25, 1936, July 10, 1936, Aug. 31, 1937, Dec. 6, 1937 (to K.D. McKellar), Oct. 3, 1947 (to Jim McCord); 7
Crab Orchard Stone Company, Inc. (1); May 11, 1933 (to H.C. Uhler); 7
Crabb, A.L., (1); July 23, 1948; 7
Crabtree, H.D., (2); May 4, 1960, May 13, 1960; 7
Craig, ~orneliue A., (2); May 25, 1933, Aug. 3, 1942; 7
Craig, Edwin w., (6); May 8, 1935, Feb. 15, 1946, Apr. 25, 1949, Dec. 20, 1950, Mar. 3, 1954, Sept. 24, 1957; 7
Creson, Larry B. Jr., (1); Apr. 23, 1961; 7
Crews, L.D., (1); Jan. 13, 1933; 7
Cripps, John, (1); ~ept. 30, 1946; 7
Criswell, Bill, (1); Apr. 21, 1961; 7
Crookes, Harold, (1); Nov. 2, 1943; 7
Crouch, Larkin E., (2); Dec. 21, 1933, May 31, 1934 (to George H. Armistead); 7
Crownover, Arthur Jr., (2); Aug. 24, 1938, July 2, 1946; 7
Crownover, Sima, {2); Nov. 1, 1937, May 24, 1957; 7
Crump, Charles M., (1); Mar. 30, 1964; 7
Cummings, Thos. L., (1, encl.); Oct. 6, 1938; 7
Currey, Brownlee 0., (4); May 26, 1937 (to Francis M. Bass), Mar. 8, 1940, Feb. 18, 1946, Jan. 13, 1949; 7
DaCosta, RObert C. Jr., (1); July 7, 1949; 7
Dailey, Fletcher Jr., (l); Sept. 24, 1933; 7
Daniel, Richard P., (4); June 30, 1933, Mar. 16, 1934, Apr. 23, 1957, Sept. 17, 1957; 7
Daniels, Stewart D., (2); Mar. 8, 1938, July 6, 1944; 7
Davidson, Donald, (l); July 17, 1948; 7
Davidson, Eugenia, (l); Nov. 24, 1952 (to John Buckingham); 7
Davidson, Philip, (2); Nov. 1, 1949 (to Bordon Browning), (n.d.); 7
Davis, Bond, (1); June 3, 1942; 7
Davis, Elizabeth, (1); July 18, 1933; 7
Davis, Frank E., (1); Nov. 1934; 7
Davis, Helen & Sam, (1); (n.d.); 7
Davis, Jefferson, (7); Dec. 30, 1953, Dec. 28, 1956, Jan. 7, 1959, Feb. 22, 1960, Nov. 29, 1960, Feb. 15, 1962, Oct. 15, 1962; 7
Davis, Lipscomb, (l); (n.d.); 7
Davis, 0. Jennings, (2); Oct. 20, 1944, Feb. 15, 1946; 7
Davis, Paul M., (1); May 9, 1934; 7
Davis, R.A., (2); Dec. 3, 1938, May 26, 1939; 7
Dawson, Robbie & Collier, (1); July 24, 1961; 7
Dean, Chas. A., (4); Mar. 9, 1932, Aug. 17, 1933, ~ept. 12, 1933, Sept. 22, 1933; 7
Dedman, Bertram C., (1); Jan. 8, 1963; 7
Deer, George, (l); July 8, 1964; 7
DeGraw, M. Bessie, (4); May 22, 1941, Sept. 12, 1941, Dec. 28, 1944, July 7, 1946; 7
DeLamater, J.N., (1); Feb. 10, 1948 (to Michael J. Bent); 7
Denney, W. Raymond, (l); May 5, 1932; 7
DePriest, Roy E., (1); Dec. 18, 1946 (to Bancroft-Whitney Company); 7
DePriest, William, (2); May 11, 1964, May 18, 1964; 7
DeWitt, Jack, (2); Mar. 19, 1956, Feb. 3, 1967 (to John Beasley); 7
Dews, Mary Harrison, (2); Jan. 6, 1962, Feb. 24, 1962; 7
Dietrich, R.W., (1); Mar. 30, 1944; 7
Dinkler, Carling, (1); Dec. 2, 1936; 7
Dittus, F.A., (1); -May 11, 1933; 7
Diver, Clarence W., (1); Jan. 21, 1957; 7
Dixon, Paul Rand, (6); Nov. 19, 1960, Nov. 30, 1960, Nov. 30, 1960 (to Madison Sarratt), Nov. 30, 1960 (to William P. Moss), Feb. 15, 1961, May 8, 1963; 7
Dobbs, Jim, (1); June 13, 1957; 7
Dobson, Allen, (2); Nov. 20, 1947 (to Harvie Branscomb), May 24, 1962; 7
Dodge, Robert G., (2); Aug. 5, 1940, Aug. 5, 1940 (to Frank A. Berry); 7
Dodson, Harlan, (1); Jan. 13, 1966; 7
Donohue, F. Joseph, (1); Apr. 26, 1956; 7
Dorsey, A.L., (5); Dec. 12, 1933, Jan. 15, 1934, May 17, 1939, June 19, 1940, Oct. 14, 1940; 7
Dortch, Nat, (1); June 5, 1963 (to J. Murphy Thomas, Jr.); 7
Dossett, Burgin E., (1); Apr. 21, 1951; 7
Douglas, Byrd, (3); Jan. 11, 1933, Mar. 15, 1947, Mar. 31, 1964; 7
Douglas, James, (1); July 11, 1942; 7
Douglas, Lee, (1); Jan. 25, 1957; 7
Dozier, Howard D., (1); Apr. 22, 1945; 7
Drake, Frank M., (1); Jan. 19, 1937; 7
Drane, Myrtle, (1); (n.d.); 7
Draughon, J.V., (1); Nov. 24, 1933 (to V.J. Alexander); 7
Driscoll, Edmund F., (1); May 8, 1941; 7
Dudney, E.L., (1); May 5, 1936 (to Walter Chandler); 7
Duggin, Marshall E., (1); May 15, 1965; 7
Dulles, John Foster, (1); (n.d.); 7
Durrett, Forrest M., (1); Oct. 9, 1964; 7
Dustin, Red, (1); (n.d.); 7
Dyer, Harry B., (1); Mar. 18, 1946; 7
Earthman, William F. Jr., (1); Oct. 20, 1961; 7
Eben, S.N., (1); Sept. 8, 1950; 7
Eberling, Ernest J., (1); -June 11, 1963; 7
Eddie, John, (l); .Nov.l8, 1962; 7
Edwards, Connelly, (1); (n.d.) (to Walton Cunningham); 7
Eichenbaum, E. Chas.; -(2); Hay 31, 1954, Dec. 29, 1954; 7
Eisenhower, Dwight D., (1); July 21, 1960 (to Dallas S. Townsend); 7
Eldridge, Thomas, (1); Aug. 28, 1964; 7
Eliot, Thomas H., (1); July 6, 1948
Elliot, Annie M., (1); June 18, 1913; 7
Elliott, Beulah, (1); Dec. 6, 1965; 7
Elliott, Don, (1); Oct. 9, 1963; 7
Elliott, Frederick C., (1); Aug. 4, 1949 (to Walter M. Morgan); 7
Elmore, Robert A., (1); May 8, 1943; 7
Elsifon, Si & Vivian, (1); Dec. 17, 1957; 7
Ely, Robert B. III, (1); Jan. 9, 1963; 7
Enlow, Robert C., (1); Jan. 7, 1939; 7
Epps, A.P., (l); July 21, 1960; 7
Eppse, Merl R., (1); Apr. 20, 1955; 7
Evans, Amon Carter, (1); Nov. 4, 1961; 7
Evans, Henry Clay Jr., (2); May 19, 1933, Aug. 14, 1933; 7
Evans, Jack, (1); May 31, 1934; 7
Evans, Marien G., (2); Apr. 19, 1949, May 20, 1949; 7
Evans, Silliman, (5); Feb. 25, 1939, Apr. 7, 1939, Nov. 28, 1939, Feb. 13, 1946, (n.d.); 7
Evans, Thos. A., (1); Nov. 23, 1918 (to F.J. Ru~on); 7
Everett, Robert A., (4); Hay 7, 1944, Nov. 9, 1945, Jan. 10, 1946, Feb. 28, 1966; 7
Evins, Joanna, (1); Jan. 3, 1958; 7
Ewing, Cecil, (1); Jan. 24, 1955; 7
Fain, J. Tyree, (2); Feb. 13, 1934, June 4, 1934; 7
Fancher, Frank T., (1); Hay 3, 1941; 7
Farmer, Fyke Jr., (1); Feb. 9, 1944; 7
Farmer, George E., (1); Apr. 22, 1944; 7
Farrell, Norman Jr., (1); Dec. 16, 1918; 7
Faubion, J.T., (1); Sept.25, 1962; 7
Feeney, J.R., (1); Hay 19, 1959; 7
Felker, Mrs. Richard, (1); (n.d.); 7
Felker, Richard, (14); Jan. 9’, 1953, June 25, 1953, Sept. 1, 1953, May 11, 1954, June 8, 1954, Oct. 1, 1954, Oct. 27~ 1954, May 18, 1962, July 2, 1962, Jan. a, 1963, Feb. 18, 1964, Apr.22, 1964 (to Bebe Felker), Apr. 22, 1964 (to Sherer Irvin), Apr. 22, 1964 (to Wilson Sims); 7
Fellrath, C.J., (1); July 6, 1962; 7
Felts, S.L., (2); Apr. 12, 1962, Dec. 9, 1963; 7
Fensterwa1d, Bernard Jr., (2); Apr. 23, 1959, Feb. 18, 1960; 7
Fincher, D.H., (5); Oct. 14, 1959, Feb. 18, 1960, July 6, 1961, Sept. 1, 1961, Sept. 12, 1961; 7
Finger, H.E. Jr., (1); Dec. 26, 1966; 7
Finney, Jas. W., (1); Sept. 23, 1943; 7
Fisher, J. Ed C., (1); Sept. 3, 1918; 7
Fleming, D.F., (1); May 28, 1947; 7
Fleming, Porter, (1); June 7, 1951; 7
Fleury, A., (1); May 13, 1934; 7
Flinn, Harold M., (1); May 24, 1943; 7
Follin, Webb, (23); Feb. 12, 1935, Sept. 18, 1935, Dec. 18, 1935, Feb. 12, 1936, Nov. 18, 1936, Mar. 23, 1937, Nov. 18, 1937, Dec. 13, 1937, Dec. 27, 1937, Oct. 30, 1938, Dec. 5, 1938, Jan. 12, 1940, Nov. 15, 1940, Nov. 19, 1940, Feb. 4, 1941, June 8, 1944, Jan. 4, 1945, Jan. 23, 1945, Jan. 8, 1946, Feb. 14, 1946, July 31, 1946, Mar. 25, 1947, Apr. 8, 1957; 7
Folsom, Victor C., (1); June 23, 1955; 7
Folts, Aubrey F., (2); Jan. 9, 1948, Jan. 20, 1948; 7
Forbes, F. Murray Jr., (1); Oct. 10, 1960; 7
Fordham, Jefferson B., (1); Apr. 22, 1955; 7
Forman, Guy, (1); Jan.17, 1951; 7
Forrester, R.C., (1); Mar. 3, 1966; 7
Forrester, Ray, (11); Feb. 23, 1950, Jan. 15, 1953, June 2, 1954, June 15, 1955, Mar. 9, 1956, July 11, 1956, Apr. 3, 1957, May 16, 1957, Nov. 19, 1959, Nov. 21, 1961, Nov. 30, 1962; 7
Forrester, W. Howell, (1); Oct. 18, 1960; 7
Fort, J. Carter, (1); Oct. 16, 1937 (to Lovick P. Miles); 7
Foster, Marshall, (l); Sept.10, 1957; 7
Foutch, Katherine, (1); Feb. 14, 1940; 7
Fowler, H. Thornton, (2); Jan. 14, 1955, May 1, 1962; 7
Fowler, Harley G., (7); May 26, 1933, Feb. 7, 1934, July 17, 1934, Oct. 9, 1941, Apr. 30, 1955, Feb. 4, 1957, June 20, .1958; 7
Fowler, J. Fort, (2); Apr. 12, 1958, June 2, 1958; 7
Fox, Henry J., (1); Feb. 8, 1957; 7
Foy, Joe H., (2); Apr. 4, 1957, Sept. 18, 1962; 7
Frank, Irene, (1); Feb. 17, 1946; 7
Frankel, Gustave, (3); Dec. 7, 1938, Dec. 13, 1938, July 15, 1949; 7
Frankel, Louis, (1); May 22, 1936; 7
Fraser, Frank, (2); May 30, 1944, Dec. 29, 1944; 7
Frazer, James S. Jr., (1); July 30, 1962; 7
Frederick, F.D., (1); Mar. 10, 1932; 7
Freese, F.O., (1); Dec 20, 1946; 7
French, J.C., (2); July 23, 1942, July 1, 1955; 7
Frierson, J. Dawson Jr., (1); Oct.11, 1958; 7
Fry, Theodore, (1); Nov. 10, 1939; 7
Fulp, J.D., (2); dept. 11, 1918, Sept. 11, 1918; 7
Fulton, Richard, (8); Jan. 10, 1964, Apr. 14, 1965, Nov. 24, 1965, Nov. 29, 1965, Nov. 29, 1965 (to Hugh Shelton, Jr.), Oct. 31, 1966, (n.d.), (n.d.); 7
Funkhouser, Frank, (1); Jan. 28, 1957; 7
Furlow, Bill Sr., (1); Feb. 5, 1938; 7
Gale, Dudley, (1); Jan. 28, 1954; 7
Gale, George J., (1); Jan.28, 1937; 7
Foster, James, (1); Jan. 15, 1962; 7
Gambrell, David H., (1); Sept. 24, 1956; 7
Gambrell, E. Smythe, (1); May 28, 1959; 7
Gardenhire, J.M., (1); Mar. 6, 1933; 7
Gardner, Edwin S., (2); Jan. 5, 1965, Aug. 22; 7
Gardner, Robt. J., (2); Dec. 22, 1937, Oct.l9, 1939; 7
Garner, Robert L., (3); June 3, 1936, July 21, 1936, Nov. 16, 1944; 7
Gault, Alma E., (1); Dec. 15, 1949; 7
Geiger, Albert J., (1); Nov. 10, 1938 (to Vernon Sharp, Jr.); 7
Geiger, John C., (2); Oct. 3, 1942, (n.d.); 7
Gentry, John A. III, (3); Sept. 14, 1960, Jan. 31, 1963, Jan. 31, 1964; 7
Gentsch, Bernhard F., (2); Hay 31, 1956, June 11, 1956; 7
Gerber, William, (1); Feb. 3, 1959; 7
Gest, J.S., (2); June 16, 1933, June 16, 1933 (to J. Conley Edwards); 7
Gibson, Jo Jr., (1); Aug. 29, 1947 (to Lawrence Howard); 7
Gilbert, C.C., (1); Feb. 29, 1944; 7
Gilbert, Chas. C.Jr., (1); Sept. 17, 1936; 7
Gilbert, Harris A., (1); Apr. 1, 1965; 7
Gill, E.G., (9); Nov. 21, 1933, Dec. 2, 1933, Oct. 9, 1934, Oct. 15, 1934, Sept. 23, 1935, Sept. 28, 1935, Sept. 20, 1941, Nov. 4, 1941, Nov. 1, 1945; 7
Gilliland, Frank H., (1); July 5, 1933; 7
Gillaland, Hod. H., (3); Apr. 17, 1931t, June 26, 1934, Aug. 22, 1934; 7
Gilmer, Ben S., (1); Feb. 3, 1959; 8
Gilreath, Sam B., (1); Apr. 14, 1941; 8
Glosser, Horton, (1); July 22, 1948; 8
Gochnauer, H. Wallis, (1); Aug. 8, 1961; 8
Godwin, Winfred L., (3); Mar. 13, 1959, Apr. 1, 1959, Apr. 15, 1959; 8
Goodman, Ben J. Jr., (1); Oct. 25, 1937; 8
Goodpasture, Ernest W., (1); Jan. 7, 1949 (to Harvie Branscomb); 8
Goodrich, Herbert .F., (1); Dec. 30, 1959; 8
Goodrich, Mary, (1); (n.d.); 8
Goodrum, Harold and Mary Ann, (1); May 31, 1960; 8
Goodwin, R.F., (1); D~c. 7, 1934; 8
Gore, Albert, (2); Sept. 19, 1934, Oct. 2, 1941; 8
Gore, John J., (2); Aug. 9, 1933, June 27, 1934; 8
Gorman, J.A., (3); June 19, 1934, June 26, 1934, June 4, 1935; 8
Gorrell, Bette J., (1); Mar. 4, 1964; 8
Gotshal, Sylvan, (1); Jan. 7, 1942; 8
Gourley, w.H., (1); Sept. 13, 1963; 8
Goza, H. Jennings Jr., (1); (n.d.); 8
Graham, Eugene, (3); July 26, 1939, July 29, 1939, Mar. 7, 1940; 8
Graham, Gladys M., (1); Mar. 30, 1919; 8
Graham, Paul, (1); Dec. 11, 1953; 8
Gray, C.W., (1); May 6, 1940; 8
Gray, Walter R., (2); Feb. 13, 1940, Feb. 26, 1940; 8
Gray, William v., (1); Feb. 13, 1960; 8
Greathouse, Joe S. Jr., (1); Nov. 28, 1961; 8
Green, Grafton, (1); May 14, 1935; 8
Greenblatt, Julian, (2); Dec. 17, 1936, Mar. 18, 1937; 8
Greene, Adron, (2); July 15, 1963, July 30, 1963; 8
Greene, John Edward, (2); July 3, 1964, Sept. 25, 1964; 8
Greene, William M., (1); Dec. 16, 1939; 8
Griffith, Charles, (1); Aug. 20, 1963; 8
Griffith, Sandra L., (1); May 26, 1963; 8
Grigsby, Hatcher M., (1); Jan. 18, 1938; 8
Gross, Ben, (1); Feb. 17, 1940 (to Tom Sims); 8
Guepe, Arthur L., (1); Aug. 24, 1962; 8
Gullion, Allen W., (1); Mar. 31, 1941; 8
Gumpert, Emil, (l); May 23, 1956; 8
Gunner, N.M., (2); Oct. 6, 1937, Nov. 30, 1937; 8
Guthrie, H.L., (1); Oct. 9, 1959; 8
Guy, James E., (1); Aug. 2, 1966; 8
Guzzo, Charlie, (1); Dec. 21, 1960; 8
Gwaltney, Corbin, (l); Mar. 12, 1965; 8
Gwinner, N.M., (l); Dec. 30, 1947; 8
Haas, Joseph F., (4); Jan. 18, 1957, Dec. 4, 1958, Jan. 14, 1959, Feb. 19, 1960; 8
Hagenwood, Biscon, (l); Jan. 12, 1947; 8
Haggard, Mary Webb, (7); Dec. 31, 1935, Jan. 22, 1936, Jan. 30, 1936, Feb. 25, 1936, Mar. 30, 1936, Feb. 14, 1940 (to William P. Moss), (n.d.); 8
Hale, Winfield B., (1); Jan. 15, 1963; 8
Hall & Benedict, (l); Jan. 3, 1933; 8
Hall, Fitzgerald, (8); Apr. 3, 1919, Sept. 22, 1933, Dec. 10, 1934, Feb. 23, 1940, Oct. 22, 1941, Feb. 6, 1944, Aug. 23, 1944, Apr. 7, 1945; 8
Hall, T. Graham, (1); (n.d.); 8
Hall, Virgil H., (1); Jan. 26, 1931; 8
Halley, Harry L.S., (l), Aug. 1, 1957; 8
Hamilton, Luther J., (1); Aug. 1, 1934; 8
Handison, W. Thomas IV, (1); (n.d.); 8
Handley, Helen, (l); (n.d.); 8
Hannon, C.W., (7); Feb. 13, 1957, Apr. 11, 1958, Nov. 30, 1959, Dec. 20, 1960, Sept. 6, 1961, Jan. 29, 1962, Sept. 12, 1962; 8
Hansell, EarlL., (l); Feb. 19, 1943; 8
Hanson, Victor H., (l); Feb. 27, 1939; 8
Hardcastle, K.C. Jr., (2); June 25, 1937, July 26, 1948; 8
Harman, Oscar W., (l); Jan. 16, 1957; 8
Harper, W.A., (5); Aug. 14, 1934, Aug. 31, 1934, Sept. 29, 1934, Oct. 1, 1934, Jan. 7, 1935; 8
Harris, A.M., (l); Oct. 6, 1941; 8
Harris, Harry N., (l); Feb. 26, 1957; 8
Harris, Tyree B., (2); July 16, 1962, Apr. 9, 1964 (to Fred Atkerson); 8
Harris, Will, (4); Aug. 1, 1939, Aug. 18, 1939, Oct. 19, 1943, Feb. 2, 1945; 8
Hart, J.E., (1); Nov. 29, 1933; 8
Hart, Joseph W., (l); Feb. 15, 1946; 8
Harwell, Mrs. Hobert E., (1); May 28, 1941; 8
Hassan, Rita, (3); Nov. 26, 1946, Mar. 13, 1947, Apr. 2, 1947; 8
Hawkes, Albert W., (1); Oct. 17, 1945; 8
Hayes, John A., (1); June 30, 1948; 8
Haynes, L.L., (1); July 27, 1954; 8
Haynes, Walter M., (2); June 10, 1935, May 26, 1955; 8
Hazelton, John H., (1); Oct. 18, 1935; 8
Healy, Harold H. Jr., (1); June 13, 1957 (to Estes Kefauver); 8
Heard, Alexander, (8); Mar. 27, 1963, Mar. 27, 1963, June 3, 1963, Dec. 18, 1963, June 20, 1964, Apr l2, 1967, Apr. 18, 1967 (to Editor, Time Magazine ), Apr. 18, 1967; 8
Heckel, Jos. E., (1); (n.d.); 8
Heflin, Jno. J., (1); (n.d.); 8
Heiskell, A.L., (2); Apr. 25, 1934, June 3, 1935; 8
Helm, Hugh B., (3); (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.); 8
Hemingway, W.L., (1); Nov. 21, 1951; 8
Henderson, John H., (1); Mar. 1, 1966; 8
Henry, W.C., (1); Oct. 14, 1953; 8
Herring, Clyde L., (1); May 12, 1937; 8
Hester, J. Thomas Jr., (1); Jan. 25, 1957; 8
Hewitt, John Vance, (1); Jan. 12, 1945; 8
Hickey, E. James, (1); Feb. 4, 1957; 8
Hickey, Rufus M. III, (2); Feb. 19, 1934, Mar. 13, 1934 8
Hilgers, Walter H., (2); Apr. 24, 1940, .11.pr. 2, 1946; 8
Hill, Mrs. Albert E., (1); June 22, 1948; 8
Hill, Henry H., (1); Jan. 12, 1954; 8
Hill, Malcolm~., (1); Oct. 17, 1945; 8
Hilldrop, Jno.w., (6); Feb. 14, 1946, July 13, 1948, Mar. 19, 1953, June 8, 1953, Thanksgiving, 1953, Feb. 23, 1955; 8
Hilliard, Moss, (2); May 12, 1946, (n.d.); 8
Hinch, R.L., (1); (n.d.); 8
Hinds, S.R., (2); May 10, 1948, May 10, 1948 (to Harold V. Hopton); 8
Hines, frank T., (1); Jan. 18, 1937; 8
Hinton, Elmer, (1); Jan. 18; 8
Hoeger, J.C. (1); Aug. 4, 1933; 8
Hoerger, J.J., (1); Mar. 7, 1934; 8
Hoffman, G.W., (1); Dec. 15, 1949; 8
Holcomb, i., (1); Sept. 12, 1940 (to Joseph w. Byrns, Jr.); 8
Holloway, G.D., (1); (n.d.); 8
Holman, John W., (1); Jan. 8, 1946; 8
Holt, A.D., (6); Aug. 11, 1954, Sept. 20, 1954, Sept. 8, 1955, Sept. 9, 1955 (to John. Ivey, Jr.), Dec. 21, 1964, May 17, 1967 (to Director of Admissions, Vanderbilt University, School of Law); 8
Holt, Elva, (1); Sept. 18, 1956 (to Riverside Sanitarium); 8
Holt, Parker, (25); June 11, 1934, July 17, 1934, Apr. 17, 1935, Sept. 15, 1935, Mar. 3, 1936, Mar. 3, 1936 (to ti.F. Paty), Mar. 27, 1936, July 16, 1936, Aug. 3, 1936, Aug. 19, 1936, Dec. 12, 1936, May 18, 1938, June 24, 1938, Jan. 6, 1942, July 1, 1942, Dec. 14, 1942, Mar. 26, 1943, Feb. 1, 1944, Aug. 29, 1944, Jan. 22, 1954, Nov. 12, 1956, Dec. 10, 1956, Nov. 13, 1959 (to Duane A. Reynolds), Jan. 20, 1960 (to John W. Emerson), Feb. 4, 1960; 8
Hooker, John J., (1); May 28, 1956; 8
Hooker, John Jay Jr., (2); Dec. 16, 1958, Jan. 31, 1964 (to William Orrick); 8
Horn, Stanley G., (1); Sept. 27, 1956 (to Mason Houghland); 8
Hoskins, Halford L., (1); July 3, 1946; 8
Houghland, Mason, (3); Oct. 30, 1956, May 14, 1957, (n.d.); 8
Housholder, Quentin L., (1); Mar. 28, 1949; 8
Howard, Laurence B., (1); Sept. 17, 1947; 8
Howard, William F., (1); May 31, 1967; 8
Howe, Harry, (1); Jan. 24, 1944; 8
Howell, Morton B., (1); July 3, 1946; 8
Howell, rt.B.c., (13); Mar. 4, 1936, May 5, 1936, Nov. 23, 1936, Mar. 11, 1937, Apr. 3, 1937 (to Kenneth D. McKellar), Apr. 26, 1937 (to James H. Kirkland), Mar. 22, 1938, Dec. 23, 1938, Jan. 9, 1939, Nov. 28, 1944, Feb. 12, 1946, Dec. 29, (n.d.); 8
Howse, Hilary E., (1); Sept. 2, 1936; 8
Howser, hugh C., (1); lee. 28, 1960; 8
Howze, Marion W., (1); Mar. 28, 1941 (to Archer L. Lerch); 8
Houston, Frank K., (7); May 21, 1948, Sept. 16, 1948, Jan. 13, 1959, May 20, 1959, Dec. 3, 1962, Apr. 2, 1963, (n.d.); 8
Houston, P.D. Jr., (1); Feb. 26, 1963; 8
Huber, Richard G., (l); Dec. l, 1954; 8
Huff, A.J., (1); May 25, 1933; 8
Hull, vordell, (14); Aug. 8, 1933, Feb. 20, 1934, Dec. 16, 1935, Feb. 1, 1938, Oct. 3, 1938, Apr. 6, 1940, May 8, 1940 (to Arch Rollow), Aug. 26, 1941, May 29 1 1943, Dec. 17, 1943 (to O,C. Carmichael), Dec. 31, 1943, Jan. 20, 1945, Nov. 17, 1945, Jan. 23, 1950; 8
Hume, William, (1); -May 5, 1936; 8
Humphrey, George M., (1); Oct. 26, 1955; 8
Hunt, Edwin .F., (2); Mar. 19, 1945, Apr. 4, 1955 (to W.P. Moss); 8
Hunt, Lester C., (1); Jan. 14, 1949 (toM. Don Clawson); 8
Hunt, S.H., (1); Oct. 26, 1937; 8
Hutchison, A.W. Jr., (1); July 31, 1961 (to Jim Nolen); 8
Hutchison, Harriet, (1); Mar. 9, 1936; 8
Hyder, Jean, (1); July 27, 1966; 8
Hydrick, Augustus s., (1); Dec. 12, 1944; 8
Ingraham, Frank C., (2); Mar. l, 1955, (n.d.); 8
Ingram, Hank, (3); Aug. 3, 1940, July 22, 1944, Jan. 31, 1946; 8
Ivey, John E. Jr., (53); Nov. 13, 1948, Jan. 21, 1949, Mar. 1, 1949 (toM. Don Clawson), May 7, 1949, May 16, 1949, May 23, 1949, June 4, 1949, June 25, 1949, July 7, 1949 (to J. Millard Smith), July 12, 1949 (toM. Don vlawson), July 15, 1949 (to J.M. Smith), Nov. 3, 1949, Jan. 10, 1950,(to J,M. Smith), Jan. 20, 1950 (to J.M. Smith), Jan. 30, 1950 (to James B. Hill), Feb. 20, 1950, Feb. 20, 1950, (to Steve Humphrey), Mar. 16, 1950 (to Gordon Browning),Apr. 28, 1950, May 23, 1950 (to Charles S. JohioU., May 27, 1950 (to C.E. Breehm), May 30, 1950 (t~ Gordon Browning), June 2, 1950, June 5, 1950 (to Harvie Branscomb), June 6, 1950, Dec. 7, 1950 (to Gordon Browning), Dec. 28, 1950 (to WalterS. Davis), Dec. 28, 1950 (to C.E. Brehm), Jan. 2, 1951, Jan. 8, 1951, Jan. 9, 1951 (to J.A. Barksdale), Jan. 16, 1951, Jan. 16, 1951 (to J.D. Williams), Jan. 16, 1951 (to F.D. Bluford(, Feb. 5, 195l,(to Gordon Browning), Mar. 9, 1951, Apr. 5, 1951, Apr. 10, 1951, Apr. 15, 1951,
Ivey, John E. Jr., co~t., Apr. 27, 1951, Aug. 31, 1951, Sept. 28, 1951, Oct. 8, 1951, Jan. 10, 1952, Feb. 14, 1952, (to Henry H. Hill), May 26, 1952, May 27, 1952, JUne 20, 1952, July 10, 1952, JUly 10, 1952, Sept. 24, 1952 (to Gordon Browning), Nov. 22, 1955, (n.d.); 8
Jackson, M.E., (1); Jan. 13, 1937; 8
Jackson, Robert H.; (1); Apr. 10, 1944; 8
Jackson. William H., (1); May 20, 1955; 8
James, Hargaret,C., (1); Dec. 23, 1949; 8
Janney, W.L., (2); Feb. 1, 1952, July 28’7 1952; 8
Jarman, Claude Sr., (1); July 15, 1948; 8
Jarrett, Lucy, (1); May 30, 1940; 8
Johnson, E.C., (1); May 14, 1937; 8
Johnson, ulenn I., (1); June 15, 1965 (to Tom Henderson); 8
Johnson, S.P., (1); Sept. 5, 1933; 8
Johnson, VictorS. Jr., (8); Mar. 24, 1955, Sept. 21, 1955, May 22, 1959, Mar. 28, 1960, Oct. 18, 1962, Apr. 13, 1966, July 20, 1966, Jan. 24, 1967; 8
Johnston, D.E., (1); May 10, 1937; 8